Guide to the Paul Ehrlich Papers SC0223
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Publications, Series 6
  - Books, Permission Forms (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Books, Permissions, Ballantine Books 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Articles, Declined Requests 1970, Folder 1 of 3 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Articles, Declined Requests 1970, Folder 2 of 3 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Articles, Declined Requests 1970, Folder 3 of 3 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Articles, Declined Requests 1971, Folder 1 of 4 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Articles, Declined Requests 1971, Folder 2 of 4 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Articles, Declined Requests 1971, Folder 3 of 4 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Articles, Declined Requests 1971, Folder 4 of 4 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Articles, Declined Requests 1971-1973 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Articles, Permission Granted – Not Used 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Articles, Permission Granted, No Fee, No Form Sent, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Articles, Permission Granted, No Fee, Form Returned 1971-1972, Folder 1 of 3 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Articles, Permission Granted, No Fee, Form Returned 1971-1972, Folder 2 of 3 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Articles, Permission Granted, No Fee, Form Returned 1971-1972, Folder 3 of 3 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Articles, Permission Granted, No Fee, Form Not Returned 1970-1973, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Articles, Permission Granted, No Fee, Form Not Returned 1970-1973, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Articles, Reprint Permission 1970-1971, Folder 1 of 3 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Articles, Reprint Permission 1970-1971, Folder 2 of 3 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Articles, Reprint Permission 1970-1971, Folder 3 of 3 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Articles, Reprint Permission 1973-1974, Folder 1 of 3 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Articles, Reprint Permission 1973-1974, Folder 2 of 3 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Articles, Reprint Permission 1973-1974, Folder 3 of 3 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Articles, Problem Permissions 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Paul Growald, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Articles, Requests for Tapes 1970-1971, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Articles, Requests for Tapes 1970-1971, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Articles, Check Receipts 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Articles, Reprint Receipts 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Articles, Permission Granted, Signed Forms Returned 1970-1973, Folder 1 of 3 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Articles, Permission Granted, Signed Forms Returned 1970-1973, Folder 2 of 3 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Articles, Permission Granted, Signed Forms Returned 1970-1973, Folder 3 of 3 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Articles, Fee Permissions Granted, Forms Not Returned 1969-1974, Folder 1 of 4 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Articles, Fee Permissions Granted, Forms Not Returned 1969-1974, Folder 2 of 4 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Articles, Fee Permissions Granted, Forms Not Returned 1969-1974, Folder 3 of 4 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Articles, Fee Permissions Granted, Forms Not Returned 1969-1974, Folder 4 of 4 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Articles, Fee Permissions Paid, A – F 1970- 1972, Folder 1 of 3 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Articles, Fee Permissions Paid, A – F 1970- 1972, Folder 2 of 3 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Articles, Fee Permissions Paid, A – F 1970- 1972, Folder 3 of 3 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Articles, Fee Permissions Paid, G – L 1970- 1972, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Articles, Fee Permissions Paid, G – L 1970- 1972, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Articles, Fee Permissions Paid, M – R 1970- 1973, Folder 1 of 4 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Articles, Fee Permissions Paid, M – R 1970- 1973, Folder 2 of 4 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Articles, Fee Permissions Paid, M – R 1970- 1973, Folder 3 of 4 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Articles, Fee Permissions Paid, M – R 1970- 1973, Folder 4 of 4 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Articles, Fee Permissions Paid, S – Z 1970- 1972, Folder 1 of 3 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Articles, Fee Permissions Paid, S – Z 1970- 1972, Folder 2 of 3 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Articles, Fee Permissions Paid, S – Z 1970- 1972, Folder 3of 3 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Articles, Pending 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Articles, Permissions RL Harriman 1968--1971, Folder 1 of 6 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Articles, Permissions RL Harriman 1968--1971, Folder 2 of 6 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Articles, Permissions RL Harriman 1968--1971, Folder 3 of 6 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Articles, Permissions RL Harriman 1968--1971, Folder 4 of 6 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Articles, Permissions RL Harriman 1968--1971, Folder 5 of 6 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Articles, Permissions RL Harriman 1968--1971, Folder 6 of 6 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Articles, Permission checks received 1970 -, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Articles, Reprint Permission, Biological Sciences Curriculum Study 1973 -, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Books, "End of Affluence" 1974 –, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Outline for Data Book on "Environment, Resources, and Population", 1971 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Stockholm Conference Eco 1972, Folder 1 of 3 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Stockholm Conference Eco 1972, Folder 2 of 3 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Stockholm Conference Eco 1972, Folder 3 of 3 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Pamphlet, "Carta Europea dell'Acqua" (Italian), 1969 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Pamphlet, "Zero Population Growth", 1970 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Pamphlet, "The Destruction of Indochina", 1970 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Pamphlet, "The World Population Situation in 1970", 1971 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Pamphlet, Pests and Pesticides, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Pamphlet, "Forum" Winter, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Pamphlet, "Vital Views of the Environment", 1970 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Bibliography, "Population", 1972 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Bibliography, "Pollution", 1972 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Article, Mademoiselle magazine, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Article, TWA Ambassador magazine, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Article, California Living magazine, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Article, India Student magazine, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Article, Saturday Review magazine, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Article, Ramparts magazine, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Article, Natural History magazine, book review, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Article, National Wildlife magazine (part of article missing), 1970 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Article, Newsweek magazine, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Article, Bulletin magazine, October, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Article, American Scientist magazine, May-June, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Article, The Plain Truth magazine, June-July, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Article, Science Activities magazine, October, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Article, Stanford Today magazine, Winter, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Article, Audubon magazine, May, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Article, Progressive magazine, April, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Article, Pacific review magazine, Spring, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Article, Bio Science magazine, May, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Article, The UNESCO Courier magazine (English), July-August, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Article, The UNESCO Courier magazine (Arabic), July-August, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Article, The UNESCO Courier magazine (Russian), July-August, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Article, The UNESCO Courier magazine (Spanish), July-August, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Article, Bulletin of Atomic Scientists magazine, May, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Article, Survival One: An Earth Anthology, June, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Manuscript, "Extinction" 1980 (Setting Copy) Chapters 1,2 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Manuscript, "Extinction" 1980 (Setting Copy) Chapters 3,4 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Manuscript, "Extinction" 1980 (Setting Copy) Chapters 5,6 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Manuscript, "Extinction" 1980 (Setting Copy) Chapter 7 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Manuscript, "Extinction" 1980 (Setting Copy) Chapter 8 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Manuscript, "Extinction" 1980 (Setting Copy) Chapter 9,10,Appendix (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Manuscript, "Extinction" 1980 (Setting Copy) Notes (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Manuscript, "Extinction" 1980 (Master Set-1st Pass) pages 1-158 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Manuscript, "Extinction" 1980 (Master Set-1st Pass) pages 160-320 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Manuscript, "Extinction" 1980 (Master Set-1st Pass) pages 322-454 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Manuscript, "Extinction" 1980 (Master Set-1st Pass) pages 456-557 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Magazine, Scientific American magazine (page 169) February 1962 (Box 6)
  - Magazine, Look magazine (page 84) January, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Magazine, Look magazine (page 42) April, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Magazine, Life magazine (page 32) April, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Magazine, McCall's magazine (page 46) July, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Magazine, The National NDC Newsletter (page 5) July, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Magazine, Bio Science magazine (page 1065) Dec, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Magazine, The Bulletin of the Atomic Scientists (page 34) October, 1979 (Box 6)
  - Magazine, Technology Review magazine (page 58) April, 1980 (Box 6)
  - Magazine, The Saturday Evening Post (page 8) Fall, 1972 (Box 6)
  - "No Deposit No Return" (page 35), 1970 (Box 7)
  - Book, "the Population Bomb", 1968 (Box 7)
  - Book, "the Population Bomb" Revised Edition, 1971 (Box 7)
  - Book, "Topics in Our Time" (page 73), 1971 (Box 7)
  - Book, "Economic Growth vs. The Environment (page 48), 1971 (Box 7)
  - Book, Breeding Ourselves to Death", (hardback, page 1), 1971 (Box 7)
  - Book, Breeding Ourselves to Death", (paperback, page 1), 1971 (Box 7)
  - Book, "Politics and Ecology" (page 282), 1972 (Box 7)
  - Book, "Sociology" (page 307), 1983 (Box 7)
  - Book, "Inquinamenti del Mare" (Italian), 1970 (Box 7)
  - Book, "Statistical Yearbook of Finland (Finnish), 1970 (Box 7)
  - Book, "La Bombe P" (French), 1971 (Box 7)
  - Book, "Population, Resources, Environment" (French), 1972 (Box 7)
  - Book, "Die Bevölkerungsbombe" (German), 1973 (Box 7)
  - Book, "Die Bevölkerungsbombe" (German), 1973 (Box 7)
  - Book, "Nüfus Bombesi" (Turkish), 1976 (Box 7)
  - Book, "De bevolkingsexplosie" (Dutch), 1971 (Box 8)
  - Book, "De bevolkingsexplosie" (Dutch), 1971 (Box 8)
  - Book, "Biology and Society" Book 1 (Japanese), 1974 (Box 8)
  - Book, "Biology and Society" Book 2 (Japanese), 1974 (Box 8)
  - Book, "Biology and Society" Book 3 (Japanese), 1974 (Box 8)
  - Book, "Biology and Society" Book 4 (Japanese), 1974 (Box 8)
  - Book, "Population, Resources, Environment (Japanese), 1975 (Box 8)
  - Book, "Population, Resources, Environment (Japanese), 1975 (Box 8)
  - Book, "No Room for Man" (page 150), 1979 (Box 8)
  - Book, "Life After 80" (page 67), 1980 (Box 8)
  - Book, "Society as It Is" (page 454), 1980 (Box 8)
  - Book, "College Health Science", 1973 (Box 8)
  - Book, "A Conversation on Population, Environment, and Human Well-Being" (page 458), 1972 (Box 9)
  - Book, "Readings in Health" (page 458), 1972 (Box 9)
  - Book, "Technology as a Social and Political Phenomenon" (page 300), 1976 (Box 9)
  - Book, "An Introduction to Sociology" (page 173), 1981 (Box 9)
  - Book, "Man in Industrial Society" (page 167), 1973 (Box 9)
  - Book, "Sociology Full Circle" (page 328), 1972 (Box 9)
  - Book, "Basic Issues in Environment" (page 145), 1972 (Box 9)
  - Book, "Population Crisis, and interdisciplinary perspective" (page 102), 1972 (Box 9)
  - Book, "What's Happening?" (page 219), 1970 (Box 9)
  - Book, "Population Environment & People" (page 8), 1971 (Box 9)
  - Book, "Critical Issues for College Health" (page 161), 1968 (Box 9)
  - Book, "Reflection/Perception" (page 342), 1971 (Box 10)
  - Book, "Man and the Environment" (Forward, page XV), 1971 (Box 10)
  - Book, "Man and the Environment" (Forward, page XV), 1971 (Box 10)
  - Book, "Scene Seventy" (page 301), 1971 (Box 10)
  - Book, "Ecocide" (page 21), 1971 (Box 10)
  - Book, "The Politics of Neglect" (page 10), 1971 (Box 10)
  - Book, "The Crisis of Survival" (Japanese), 1970 (Box 10)
  - Book, "Voyages" (Forward, page IX), 1971 (Box 10)
  - Book, "Science, Technology, and Freedom" (page 210), 1974 (Box 10)
  - Book, "Marriage Means Encounter" (page 57), 1973 (Box 10)
  - Book, "Marriage Means Encounter" (page 57), 1973 (Box 10)
  - Book, "Society and Environment: The Coming Collision" (page 269), 1972 (Box 10)
  - Book, "The Quality of Life in America" (page 13), 1973 (Box 10)
  - Book, "Issues 4: Critical Questions for the 70's", 1972 (Box 11)
  - Book, "The Everlasting Universe" (page 152), 1971 (Box 11)
  - Book, "Notes for the Future" (page 46), 1975 (Box 11)
  - Book, "Reading America" (page 123), 1978 (Box 11)
  - Book, "Reading America" (page 123), 1978 (Box 11)
  - Book, "Project Survival" (page 32), 1970 (Box 11)
  - Book, "Project Survival" (page 32), 1970 (Box 11)
  - Book, "Man in the Natural World" (page 121), 1973 (Box 11)
  - Book, "Man in the Natural World" (page 121), 1973 (Box 11)
  - Book, "College Reading and College Writing" (page 482), 1971 (Box 11)
  - Book, "Appleseeds and Beercans" (page 179), 1974 (Box 11)
  - Book, "Krusbuch" (German) (page 72), 1973 (Box 11)
  - Book, "The Hastings Law Journal" (page 1345), 1972 (Box 11)
  - Book, "The Hastings Law Journal" (page 1345), 1972 (Box 11)
  - Manuscript, "Extinction" 1981 (#6763) pages 1-158 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Manuscript, "Extinction" 1981 (#6763) pages 160-320 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Manuscript, "Extinction" 1981 (#6763) pages 322-454 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Manuscript, "Extinction" 1981 (#6763) pages 456-557 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Manuscript, "Extinction" Corrections 1981 (#6763) (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Manuscript, "Extinction" Index 1981 (#6763) pages 1-39 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Manuscript, "Extinction" Index 1981 (#6763) pages 40-78 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Manuscript, "Extinction" 1981 (Master set-2nd pass) pages 1-158 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Manuscript, "Extinction" 1981 Master set-2nd pass) pages 160-320 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Manuscript, "Extinction" 1981 Master set-2nd pass) pages 322-454 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Manuscript, "Extinction" 1981 Master set-2nd pass) pages 456-557 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Manuscript, "Extinction" Index 1981 Master set-2nd pass) (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Book, "Arizona Highways", 1970 (Box 13)
  - Book, "Ecological Crisis" (page 3), 1970 (Box 13)
  - Book, "The Whole Idea Catalog" (page 37), 1971 (Box 13)
  - Book, "Eco-Crisis" (page 33), 1970 (Box 13)
  - Book, "Silent Spring (Forward, page XV) 1962 (Box 13)
  - Book, "Annual Editions Readings in Biology" (page 21), 1973 (Box 13)
  - Book, "Project Survival" (page 32), 1970 (Box 13)
  - Magazine, Ramparts Ecology Special, May, 1970 (Box 13)
  - Pamphlet, Biological Conservation, 1969 (Box 13)
  - Book, "Toward Century 21" (page 53), 1970 (Box 14)
  - Book, "Health in a Changing Society", 1976 (Box 14)
  - Magazine, "The Quarterly Review of Biology (page 48) March, 1978 (Box 14)
  - Magazine, "The Sciences (page 27) September, 1978 (Box 14)
  - Magazine, "The Stanford Magazine (page 20) Spring, 1978 (Box 14)
  - Book, "Un Pianeta Non Basta" ("The Population Bomb in Italian), 1991 (Box 14)
  - Book, "Per Salvare Il Pianeta" (Healing the Planet in Italian), 1992 (Box 14)
  - Book, "Pioneers of Ecology" (page 84-89), 1971 (Box 14)
  - Book, "The People's Almanac Presents the Book of Predictions" (page 126), 1981 (Box 15)
  - Book, "Born to Starve" (page 15), 1970 (Box 15)
  - Book, "Philosophers of the Earth" (page 140), 1972 (Box 15)
  - Book, "Critiques of Contemporary Rhetoric" (pages 14, 111-129), 1972 (Box 15)
  - Book, "The Rhetorical Dialogue" (pages 325-327, 336-346), 1972 (Box 15)
  - Book, "The Contemporary Scene" (pages 13, 38, 234), 1970 (Box 15)
  - Book, "The Study of Society, Second Edition" (pages 448-451), 1977 (Box 15)
  - Book, "Global Resources" (page 98), 1991 (Box 16)
  - Book, "L'Avenir a Reclulons (French), 1970 (Box 16)
  - Book, "Instructor's Guide to Health in a Changing Society" (Box 16)
  - Book, "Animal Adaptation" 1964 (Box 16)
  - Book, "This Good, Good Earth, our Fight for Survival", 1971 (Box 16)
  - Book, "Core Concepts in health", 1979 (Box 16)
  - Book, "Instructor's Resource Guide for Core Concepts in health", 1979 (Box 16)
  - Book, "Die Umwelt bewahren" (German) (page 35), 1989 (Box 16)
  - Book, "Nuclear Weapons and the Future of Humanity" (2 copies) (page 85), 1986 (Box 16)
  - Book, "Revista de la Escuela Nacional de Inteligencia" (Spanish) (page 87), 1992 (Box 17)
  - Book, "Populi, Journal of the United Nations Population Fund" (page 20), 1989 (Box 17)
  - Book, "The Endangered Kingdom" (page V), 1989 (Box 17)
  - Book, "Sources, Notable Selections in Sociology" (page 151) 1993 (Box 17)
  - Book, "Global Change and our Common Future" (page 19), 1989 (Box 17)
  - Book, "Population Control Through Nuclear Pollution" (page VII), 1970 (Box 17)
  - Book, "Taking Sides: Clashing Views on Controversial Issues (page 108), 1983 (Box 17)
  - Book, "Humanity in the Shadow of the Bomb" (Hebrew), 1987 (Box 17)
  - Book, "The Bedford Reader", 1985 (Box 18)
  - Book, "Aggression and Evaluation" (page 274), 1973 (Box 18)
  - Book, "Der lautlose Tod" (German) ("Extinction, The Causes and Consequences of the Disappearance of Species") (2 copies), 1983 (Box 18)
  - Book, "Utrotning" (Swedish) ("Extinction, The Causes and Consequences of the Disappearance of Species") (2 copies), 1981 (Box 18)
  - Book, "Befolknings-Bomben" (Norwegen) ("The Population Bomb") (2 copies), 1969 (Box 18)
  - Pamphlet, World Affairs Journal (page 108) 1993 (Box 18)
  - Pamphlet, RSA Journal (page 6) 1994 (Box 18)
  - Pamphlet, Peache, Health and Development, 1991 (Box 18)
  - Pamphlet, Our Planet 1994 (Box 18)
  - Pamphlet, The Population Riddle 1994 (Box 18)
  - Book, "The Silent Bomb" (page IV), 1977 (Box 19)
  - Book, "Befolknings Explosionen" (Swedish) ("the Population Bomb") (2 copies), 1971 (Box 19)
  - Book, "Die Bevolkerungs-bombe" (German) ("The Population Bomb"), 1971 (Box 19)
  - BookBevolkerungs-wachstum und Umweltkrise" (German) ("Population, Resourdes, environment") 1971, " (Box 19)
  - Book, "La Surchauffe de la Croissence" (French), 1974 (Box 19)
  - Book, "Population, Resources, Environment (Japanese), 1970 (Box 19)
  - Book, "The Pesticide Controversy" (Japanese), 1984 (Box 19)
  - Book, "Introduction to Insect Biology and Diversity" (Hebrew) (2 copies), 1971 (Box 19)
  - Book, "Selected Readings in Introductory Sociology" (page 78), 1981 (Box 20)
  - Book, "On the Fate of the Earth" (page 103), 1982 (Box 20)
  - Book, "Making it Happen" (page 45), 1982 (Box 20)
  - Book, "Population" (page 13), 1973 (Box 20)
  - Book, "The Environmental Crisis" (page 47), 1970 (Box 20)
  - Book, "Environmental Essays on the Planet as a Home" (page 252), 1971 (Box 20)
  - Book, "Molocules" (page 63), 1971 (Box 20)
  - Book, "Voices of Survival" (page 181), 1986 (Box 20)
  - Book, "Environmental Challenges" (page 1), 1986 (Box 20)
  - Book, "Texas Quarterly" (page 43), 1968 (Box 21)
  - Book, "The Visible Scientists" (page 11), 1975 (Box 21)
  - Book, "Purpose and Process" (page 447), 1989 (Box 21)
  - Book, "News that Stayed News" (page 3), 1986 (Box 21)
  - Pamphlet, "The Amicus Journal" (page 20), 1984 (Box 21)
  - Pamphlet, "The Amicus Journal" (page 12), 1981 (Box 21)
  - Pamphlet, "The Co-Evolution Quarterly" (page 21), 1984 (Box 21)
  - Pamphlet, "ZPG, An Idea with a Future", 1980 (Box 21)
  - Book, "A Scientific Throry of Culture" 1944 (Box 22)
  - Book, "King Solomon's Ring" 1952 (Box 22)
  - Book, "Man's Discovery of his Past" 1962 (Box 22)
  - Book, "Shantung Compound" 1966 (Box 22)
  - Book, "The Human Revolution" 1965 (Box 22)
  - Book, "The New Golden Bough" 1959 (Box 22)
  - Book, "The Nature and Nurture of Behavior", 1973 (Box 22)
  - Book, "Habitat, Economy and Society" 1963 (Box 22)
  - Book, "The Science of Culture" 1949 (Box 22)
  - Book, "The Naked Ape" 1967 (Box 22)
  - Book, "Dadalus" Summer 1961 (Box 22)
  - Book, "The Prevalence of People" 1962 (Box 22)
  - Book, "The Georgia Review" (page 223), 1991 (Box 22)
  - Book, "The Territorial Imperative" 1966 (Box 23)
  - Book, "The Biosocial Nature of Man" 1956 (Box 23)
  - Book, "Selected Readings in the Social Sciences" (page 152), 1973 (Box 23)
  - Book, "Social Psychology" 1965 (Box 23)
  - Book, "Social Groups of Monkeys, Apes and Man", 1970 (Box 23)
  - Book, "Amazon Cosmos", 1971 (Box 23)
  - Book, "Sociology: The Study of Man in Adaptation", 1973 (Box 23)
  - Pamphlet, Instructor's Manual to "Sociology: The Study of Man in Adaptation", 1973 (Box 23)
  - Book, "The Hunting Peoples", 1971 (Box 23)
  - Book, "Man and Culture" 1957 (Box 23)
  - Book, "The Story of the American Indian" 1927 (Box 24)
  - Book, "The Dispossessed Majority", 1981 (Box 24)
  - Book, "Scientific American Readings in Social Sciences" Volume 1, 1969 (Box 24)
  - Book, "Scientific American Readings in Social Sciences" Volume 2, 1969 (Box 24)
  - Book, "On Growth" (page 78), 1974 (Box 25)
  - Book, "American Zoologist" (page 375), 1985 (Box 25)
  - Book, "The Process Reader" (page 48), 1986 (Box 25)
  - Book, "The Essay" (page 125), 1986 (Box 25)
  - Magazine, Panorama (Dutch) (page 28) July, 1970 (Box 25)
  - Magazine, McCalls (page 46) July, 1970 (Box 25)
  - Magazine, The Listener (page 215) August, 1970 (Box 25)
  - Magazine, Look, April, 1970 (Box 25)
  - Magazine, Life, January, 1970 (Box 25)
  - Magazine, Life (page 30) April, 1970 (Box 25)
  - Newspaper, California Living, January 11, 1970 (Box 25)
  - Newspaper, California Living (page 6), January 4, 1970 (2 copies) (Box 25)
  - Newspaper, New York Times Review (page 2) April, 1970 (Box 25)
  - Manuscript, "The Machinery of Nature" (no date) (Box 25)
  - Manuscript, "The Golden Door" (rough draft), 1979 (Box 25)
  - Manuscript, "The Golden Door" (galley proof), 1979 (Box 25)
  - Book, "Ants, Indians, and Little Dinosaurs" (pg 310), 1975 (Box 25)
  - Book, "Balance and Biosphere" (pg. 59), 1971 (Box 25)
  - Book, "Americans and Environment" (pg. 105), 1971 (Box 25)
  - Book, "Politics and Environment" (pg. 13), 1970 (Box 25)
  - Book, "Human Biology" (pg. 26), 1970 (Box 25)
  - Book, "Viewpoints" (pg. 200), 1972 (Box 25)
  - Book, "Confrontation, Issues of the 70s" (pg. 367), 1971 (Box 25)
  - Book, "Sunshine and Smoke" (pg. 484), 1971 (Box 25)
  - Book, "The Population Bomb (updated)" 1978 (2 copies) (Box 25)
  - Book, "The Arthur Godfrey Environmental Reader" (pg. 171), 1970 (Box 25)
  - Book, "New World or No World" (pg. 17), 1970 (Box 25)
  - Book, "The American Population Debate" (pg. 21), 1971 (Box 25)
  - Book, "The Crisis of Survival" (pg. 237), 1970 (Box 25)
  - Book, "No Deposit No Return" (pg. 35), 1969 (Box 25)
  - Book Review, "Population, Resources, Environment" 1970-1972, Folder 1 of 5 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Book Review, "Population, Resources, Environment" 1970-1972, Folder 2 of 5 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Book Review, "Population, Resources, Environment" 1970-1972, Folder 3 of 5 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Book Review, "Population, Resources, Environment" 1970-1972, Folder 4 of 5 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Book Review, "Population, Resources, Environment" 1970-1972, Folder 5 of 5 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Articles on "Population, Resources, Environment" 1970-1972, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Articles on "Population, Resources, Environment" 1970-1972, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence on "Population, Resources, Environment" 1970-1971 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Book Reviews and Articles on "The Population Bomb" 1968-1971, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Book Reviews and Articles on "The Population Bomb" 1968-1971, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Article, Stanford Today, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Book Reviews "How to be a Survivor"1971 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Article, "Morality and the University", 1969 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Article, "Population and Panaceas", 1968 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Article "Famine 1975 – Fact or Fallacy", 1968 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Article "Birth Control: Too Little and Much Too Late", 1968 (Box 26, Folder 16)